A place for the tainted
nothing but a sound
I try to be frank with you
but words won't leave my mouth
I'd lie if I could take little more
What was I resting for?
Some day
there's a point of break where I will beg me to stay
Where I was before my feet kept missing the brakes
Thousand miles an hour, I come back home and I fade
(fade)
I have a stone that's crushing me on top of my chest
I pray for peace e- every time I walk to my bed
Oh how I wish to tell you something worth your time here with me
already breaking as the person that I'm trying to be
For every time I forced myself to push through my bounds
I hear a cry, a child in me, that wants to be proud
I said it's love until I realized it's hate in disguise
I hate myself for times I wasn't able making it right
ooh
I take the pain and lock it deeply
Cause I deserve it!
I take my shame and lock it deeply
I take the stress and lock it deeply
Cause I deserve it!
I took my state and kept it in me
Cause I'm so "perfect"!
I take the pain and lock it deeply
Cause I deserve it!
I take my shame and lock it deeply
I take the stress and lock it deeply
Cause I deserve it!
I took my state and kept it in me
Cause I'm so "perfect"!!
music
When I close my eyes
I can feel my heart, it's pushing now
Pressure me all night
Wonder what the fuck I'm doing now
I don't wanna try
I don't wan-
to force myself all out
I just want the fight
I just want the fight to settle down
I just want a night
I just want a night to let it out
I just wanna cry